(Sheldon:)...where women and men of all races
and creeds work side by side as equals.
(Leonard:)You mean where they were advanced
enough to invent an interstellar warp drive...
(Leonard:)...but a black lady
still answered the space phone?
(Howard:)Oh, I did spend a lot of my shower time
with Lieutenant Uhura.
(Sheldon:)Howard's disturbing recollections aside...
(Sheldon:)...I don't appreciate being forced
to do banal committee work.
(Leonard:)I know. You're too smart for this.
(Sheldon:)Exactly. It's like asking the Human Torch
to heat up your frozen burrito.
(Leonard:)Got it. All right, I'm thinking one way
to counter bias in the peer-review process...
(Leonard:)...is for papers to be submitted
under gender-neutral names...
(Leonard:)...like S. Smith instead of Samantha Smith.
(Sheldon:)I suppose there is a history
of professional women...
(Sheldon:)...using their initials
so as not to be pre-judged.
(Sheldon:)Harry Potter's J.K. Rowling,
uh, Star Trek's D.C. Fontana.
(Howard:)Van Nuys pole-dancer, D.D. Melons.
(Howard:)All right. I think we've really helped
women today. Let's fire up the Xbox.
(Leonard:)Don't make this a school project
where I'm the smart kid doing the work...
...while the slackers sit and watch.
We're not. You're the smart kid
doing all the work...
(Sheldon:)...while the even smarter kids
sit back and watch.
(Howard:)So you think I'm one of the smarter kids?
(Sheldon:)No, you're a tool I was using
to make my point.